#### BROCK FREEMAN

Phone: 806-790-0683 | Email: brockfreeman7@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/brock-freeman-9aa171152/ GitHub: https://github.com/Bfree22

### Summary

Business Analyst with a background in Marketing and Business Administration. Motivated entrepreneur from West Texas with a passion for discovering trends and building reports. Helped two small startups scale from hundreds to thousands of online users by using analytical tools and marketing campaigns on Hootsuite. Data-driven analyst with 4 years project management and business relations experience. In 2018, co-founded a mobile and web application called Outserved, which specializes in custom geo-fence marketing and data mining for local businesses. The ability to work with small to mid-sized databases and conduct detailed reports and insights to help scale a business, would be a strong addition to the team.

#### **Technical Skills**

Languages: Python, Pandas, SQL, Solidity Software: Hootsuite, Tableau, Jupyter Notebook Databases: PostgresQL, AWS, Back4app

### **Projects**

## Outserved Reports | https://github.com/Bfree22/Outserved-Reports

- Build dashboards to show user in-app activity on the Outserved app.
- Calculate the average time a user enters a business location.
- Tools used: Python, Pandas, Pyviz
- https://www.outserved.com/

### EV Sentiment Trading I https://github.com/Bfree22/EV\_Sentiment\_Trading

- Analyze twitter sentiment amongst various tweets to determine if there was a way to predict stock price movement.
- Use NLP to find the most talked about EV stocks and tweets to compare with stock price.
- Tools + techniques used: NLP, Python, Pandas, Plotly

### Portfolio Risk Simulator | https://github.com/Bfree22/Custom-portfolio-Risk-Return-Calculator

- Portfolio risk / return calculator with portfolio simulation for portfolios to weigh out risk between crypto and stock assets.
- Clean the data obtained from the API so it could be used for analysis.
- Implement Monte Carlo simulation with adjusted risk-level and investment amount
- Tools used: Python, Pandas, Matplotlib

## Experience

Marketing Manager 2019 – 2020

**Agrellus** Lubbock, TX

Manage content and budget for all social channels to optimize successful marketing strategies. Increase site and app activity by over 300% YTD using Hootsuite and Facebook Analytics. Work collectively with the outbound marketing team to ensure the content post and theme was similar across all channels.

# **Co-Founder / Business Analyst**

2018 - 2019

Outserved / Local LBK

Lubbock, TX

Conduct reviews and reports on business developments to minimize errors, ensuring spending is maintained and timelines are met. Effectively present in-store activity from geo-fences to local franchise owners and small business clients. Outserved recently integrated with Local LBK early 2021 to provide business insights and customer analytics to it's 100+ partners.

### **Education**

**Fintech Bootcamp Certificate: Southern Methodist University**, Dallas, TX **2021**A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in VBA, Python, SQL, Big Data, Ethereum, Blockchain, and Machine Learning.

**BA General Studies: Texas State University,** San Marcos, TX 3 Minors: Art, Business Administration, Fashion Merchandising

2016 - 2019